const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
    answer: "90°",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 60° and angle2 = 60°?",
    answer: "60°",
  },
  {
    question: "A triangle can have?",
    answer: "One right angle",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following can form a right angled triangle?",
    answer: "12, 16, 20",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following triangles are always similar?",
    answer: "Equilateral",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If one angle of the triangle is obtuse, then which one of the following is the possible measure of the remaining angles?",
    answer: "80°",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If the largest angle in a triangle is 70°, what is the least possible value of the smallest angle of the triangle?",
    answer: "10°",
  },
  {
    question: "The perimeter of scalene triangle with sides a, b, c is",
    answer: "a + b + c",
  },
  {
    question: "A scalene triangle has ___ lines of symmetry",
    answer: "0",
  },
  {
    question:
      "There is a right triangle PQR where: angle Q = 90°; angle P = angle R. What is the measure of angles P and R?",
    answer: "45°",
  },
];
